I've mentioned this a few times over the last couple months and it seems to always raise some eyebrows and spawn question marks
so I figured I'll just make a whole video here talking about it. It's true, I bought a farm and I don't mean that as a euphemism for I died.
I'm still very much alive in fact, I default into a good old-fashioned red-blooded patriot living off the Lord's titty out here.
So I've now got a lot of acres under my belts. I've even got some classic overalls in and everything and trust me when I slap that get up on it's a whole new ball game.
It looked like a $10 stripper you found outside of Walmart. There is something about my physiognomy that is just not conducive to farmer attire but I'm gonna brute force it till it looks good on me.
Point is I do have a farm now and I no longer have the warehouse which is very sad to say because the warehouse was a huge part of my life for the last almost five years now.
It served its purpose well. It was an amazing headquarters full of fun and whimsy fucking five years ago almost we got that bad boy and man did we turn that into a special place.
That was heaven on earth. All started with this video here riding around our motorized gaming chairs. We even debuted the Moby huge mobile there, the apotheosis of engineering.
We even had our own fucking wrestling league wrestling ring in there putting on our own productions. It was amazing.
I don't know how many total videos were filmed at the warehouse but it has to be like 500 if I had to spitball and guess and they're all bangers turbo bangers even.
We did of course give the warehouse a swan song. We did a little something special as a group on the other channel for a little murder mystery.
Feel free to check that out. I think it was a lot of fun and it was a nice little bond voyage to the warehouse.
You might be wondering well Charles if you love it so much why didn't you marry it? Why why don't you have the warehouse any longer?
It's because there's a lot of things that I want to do now that I just couldn't at the warehouse anymore namely building things on it.
There are certain things you cannot do when it comes to a warehouse space without getting into the nitty gritty.
No need to dive into the weeds and there's just a lot that I want to be able to have the freedom to do.
So the question naturally becomes what's the goal of the farm?
I have a lot of ideas for the land some of which are already actively working on and I'll be able to show you pretty soon.
That won't be today but soon and some of those ideas do of course include like actual farming activities growing crops.
Shit like that have a nice array of like orange trees and all kinds of things there and that does include having animals on the land as well.
Not like for the sake of food production or anything like that I'm not trying to create like some kind of self-sufficient
it's sovereign nation it not like some kind of cult facility or anything I'm not trying to make like fucking rapture out of bio shock.
I'm talking about housing some good old-fashioned barnyard animals. You know like maybe sheep.
We could share the sheep and spin our own jackets out of the wall.
Sheep like to be sheared from what I understand of course I'm not a fucking sheep whisper but that's what I always hear.
Stuff like that maybe even a horse or a horse or two and I could learn how to horseback ride.
Probably really hurt myself. Hopefully it doesn't end up kicking me in the chest and killing me instantly but like stuff like that it could be fun.
But it's not just like general farming activities that's not the entire goal of the land.
I really want the property of service like the one stop shop for all of the content that we do where typically we have to spread out across Florida to access some of it like gun ranges.
There are gun ranges in Tampa sure but they are very strict on what you're allowed to shoot there.
So the gun ranges that you've seen in the videos I posted with like the wild weapons that we've used we've had to drive like 45 minutes to an hour out of Tampa to very specific locations in order to do that.
I would love to not have to do that and instead have a gun range on my property where we can use whatever weapons we want in our own privacy.
And that is something that we are actively working on on the land right now.
Another thing that I've always wanted to be able to have access to without having to drive like hours away is a forge.
Like we all did some blacksmithing we posted a video on that a while ago and we all really liked it Danny in particular.
So I'd love to just build a fucking forge on the farmland that we could all just go and forge some weapons and sometimes maybe even have our own forge then fire kind of show.
Just wacky fun shit that is only possible to build on this amount of land.
And of course like I said I do want farming like actual like farming and agricultural stuff to be like an integral part of it but it's not the sole goal.
And one thing that we've already got which I'll be able to show you pretty soon that we've already finished is I've been gaming a lot as all of you know moist critical gaming official best fucking gaming channel on YouTube go subscribe.
I've been gaming a lot and one of the things that I did day one on the land is build out the barn into gaming pods for me and my friends to do.
I've been playing a lot of gaming content and so I plan on going full-chub into gaming even harder and it's not just that it is more than just gaming in the barn.
It is also built out for our esports watch parties which will be a lot of fun there.
It is also built out for skill check our nerdy paradise where it's mainly card games and D&D.
So magic the gathering one piece all of that is also there on a different floor.
It's just extremely nice to be able to build out these kind of things on this kind of land and like I said we are going to be getting animals in fact we have a few on the way.
I'll introduce you to them when they get there and that's probably when I'll do like a tour of the farm which I haven't really done yet.
I filmed a few videos on the farm already like with the Nile Red collab that was on the farm the car bubbles that was also on a piece of the land like we've been actively filming there and I am to do significantly more there.
Even more there than we ever did at the warehouse because hopefully we'll be able to do pretty much anything imaginable on the land.
Yeah that's kind of the gist of it that's kind of the nutshell summary of everything here.
I'm going to miss the warehouse but I'm very excited for the the farm arc here so yeah that's really about it.
See you.